# Ye Htet Aung

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Engineer with a six-year background in building business web applications. Specializes in JavaScript, including frameworks like Node.js, Vue.js, and Nuxt.js. A self-motivated and passionate about computer science, also familiar with Ruby on Rails and Python.

#### **CONTACT INFORMATION**

Location: Bangkok, Thailand Mobile: +66 81 516 8397 Email: yqxan18@qmail.com

LineID: tonyye99

Website: vehtetaung.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/ye-htet-aung

GitHub: github.com/tonyye99

LeetCode: leetcode.com/tony\_vh99

Upwork: Upwork

#### SKILLS

**Programming Languages** 

Proficient in: JavaScript, and TypeScript. Working knowledge: Ruby, Python, MySQL.

#### **Technologies**

Proficient in: Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB.

Working knowledge: Vuex, Pinia, React, Next.js, Nuxt.js, Vite, Vitest, Jest, Cypress, Ruby on Rails, ESLint, Babel, Prettier, Git.

### **Services**

Common Amazon Web Services, Basic Google Cloud Services, Heroku, Docker, Netlify, Vercel, Strapi, Firebase, Supabase, GitHub Actions.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

PROFESSY INC., Japan | Software Engineer (Remote) | Mar 2021– Sep 2023

- I worked with a 6-person development team, focusing on creating and maintaining the company's flagship product, resulting in enhanced product performance and customer satisfaction.
- Built a SaaS application using Nuxt.js and TailwindUI. Created a complete full-stack workflow using Amazon Elastic Container Service and Docker.
- Technologies used: Nuxt.js, Angular, Coffee Script, Node.js, Express.js, Amazon Simple Storage Service, Amazon Elastic Container Service with Docker containers.

Myanmar Media Linkage Co., Ltd, Myanmar | Senior Software Engineer | Jul 2020– Jan 2021

- Maintained a music streaming web application, ensuring its continuous operation and enhancing user experience.
- Developed and maintained a Node.js API, serving as an essential internal tool for the PHP backend team. It is designed to send SMS to the customer of the music streaming web application developed by the PHP backend team.
- Technologies used: Vue.js, Node.js, Express.js, Amazon Simple Storage Service, and Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud.

Myanmar High Society Co., Ltd, Myanmar | Software Engineer | Dec 2017 – Jan 2020

- Contributed to a 6 person development team as a Junior to build an order management project that used data from SalesForce by extracting Excel and PDF files.
- Worked on a web application project as a Node.js backend engineer to coordinate with the mobile development team and also lead the frontend team which heavily used the browser's canvas API to create and edit images imported by the user.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Computer Science in Software Engineering**

University of Computer Studies Mandalay, Dec 2009 – Dec 2012.

## **PROJECTS**

TweetsGen | Al Tweets Generator

- TweetsGen is a dynamic and innovative project designed to simplify and streamline the process of generating tweet ideas effortlessly.
- Used by over 100 users over the last year.
- Built with Nuxt.js, and NaiveUI and hosted using RailWay.app.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Meta Front-end Developer | 2023

- Developed a comprehensive understanding of front-end web development.
- Built a modern React app using Vite and designed its UIUX using Figma from scratch.
- Learned the knowledge of the workflow of a modern front-end developer through guidance from a Meta professional.